[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "8 + 8",
        "choices": [10, 2, 16, 25],
        "correct": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "4 + 4",
        "choices": [2, 5, 8, 3],
        "correct": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "6 + 6",
        "choices": [8, 4, 12, 12],
        "correct": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "5 + 4",
        "choices": [7, 1, 9, 5],
        "correct": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "5 + 5",
        "choices": [9, 6, 10, 20],
        "correct": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "10 + 1",
        "choices": [10, 0, 11, 25],
        "correct": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "8 + 2",
        "choices": [2, 9, 10, 3],
        "correct": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "7 + 7",
        "choices": [8, 4, 9, 14],
        "correct": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "12 + 4",
        "choices": [7, 8, 16, 5],
        "correct": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "11 + 11 ",
        "choices": [5, 0, 22, 3],
        "correct": 22
    }
]